A Finding Aid to the Ivan C. Karp Personal Papers and OK Harris Works of Art gallery records, 1960-2014, in the Archives of American Art AAA.okharr
Archives of American Art
- Artists' Files, 1967-2014; Series 4; 34 Linear feet Boxes 4-38, 80
  - Artists' Files - Past, 1967-2014; 4.2
    - Artists' Files, Past - Group B (Box 27)
      - Okshteyn, Shimon, 1995-2005 (Box 32, Folder 37)
      - Olsen, Sven-Erik, circa 2012 (Box 32, Folder 38)
      - Ossi, James M., 1981-1992 (Box 32, Folder 39)
      - Owens, Warren, 1972-1981 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - Oz, Avital, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - Perkel, Gregory, 2013; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - Poindexter, Ethel, 2011; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - Posen, Stephen, 1970s (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - Potters, Ed, 2012; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - Pratt, Vernon, 1972 (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Prythero, Tim, 1990-2013 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - Quincoces, Alejandro, 2003-2010 (Box 33, Folder 9-10)
      - Raab, Gail, 1997-2007; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - Radetsky, Jack, 2012-2013; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - Ramanaskas, Dalia, 1973-1977 (Box 33, Folder 13-14)
      - Richardson, Judy, 2013; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - Roth, Cora, 2001-2007 (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - Roth, Frank, undated (Box 33, Folder 17)
      - Rowley, Susan Ferrari, 2007-2012; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 18)
      - Rubins, Nancy, 1979-1983 (Box 33, Folder 19-21)
      - Runquist, Tollef, 2012-2013; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 33, Folder 22)
      - Russell, Jeff, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 23-24)
      - Sandman, Jo, 1973-1983 (Box 33, Folder 25-29)
      - Schottenfeld, Daniel, 2013 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Schumaker, Ward, 2011-2013; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - Schwartz, Buky, 1976-1990 (Box 34, Folder 3-5)
      - Scott, Arden, 1974-1975 (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - Schemchuk, Michael, 2005-2010; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - Shaffer, Mary, 2013; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - Siler, Todd, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - Sloane, Louise P., 1995-2011 (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - Sorce, Anthony, 2009; Includes 1 electronic disc (CD) (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - Sorcio, Roger, 1976-1979 (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - Souza, Al, 1974-1987 (Box 34, Folder 13-17)
      - Spatz-Rabinowitz, Elaine, 2002-2008 (Box 34, Folder 18)
      - Spratt, Fred, 1976 (Box 34, Folder 19)
      - Stavitsky, Ellen, 1997-2010; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 20)
      - Stella, Frank, 1968-1974 (Box 34, Folder 21)
      - Sunseri, Don, 1973 (Box 34, Folder 22)
      - Tallman, John, 2009-2012 (Box 34, Folder 23)
      - Taylor, Richard, 2007-2011; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 24)
      - Taylor, Stephen, 2006-2007 (Box 34, Folder 25)
      - Tescher, James C., 2012 (Box 34, Folder 26)
      - Thiele, Robert, 1977-1978 (Box 34, Folder 27)
      - Thomas, John Mikel, 1977-2011 (Box 34, Folder 28)
      - Tisdell, Cliff, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 29)
      - Tobin, Steve, circa 2005 (Box 34, Folder 30)
      - Tuck, Norman, 1970s (Box 34, Folder 31)
      - Turtz, Marilyn, 2012-2014; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 32)
      - Ulrich, Suzanne, 2000-2010; Includes 5 electronic discs (CD) (Box 34, Folder 33-34)
      - Warhol, Andy, circa 1969 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - Warren, Shelley, 1986 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - Watt, Roger, 2014; Includes 2 electronic discs (CD) (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Weiner, Leslie, 1980-1983 (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Weller, Ted, 1977-1984 (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Wiener, Sam, 1978-1984 (Box 35, Folder 6-7)
      - Wilson, Wallace, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - Wholley, Jay, 1975-1980 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Wood, Tanya, 2013 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Woodburn, Stephen, 1970-1980 (Box 35, Folder 11-12)
      - Zapkus, Kes, 2008-2014; Includes 4 electronic discs (CD) (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Oversized Material - Group B, John DeAndrea, from Box 29, Folder 21, 1980s (Box 80)
    - Artists' Files, Past - Group C (Box 35)
      - Ackerson, Bruce, 1982-2009 (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Algardi, Alessandro, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Alongi, Allan, 1996-1998 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Almela, Ramon, 1992-1997 (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - Appel, Eric, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 18)
      - Arman, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 19)
      - Aronson, Marc, 2009 (Box 35, Folder 20)
      - Balmuth, L. L., 1995-1997 (Box 35, Folder 21)
      - Bañuelos, Antonio, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 22)
      - Barnes, Curt, 2002 (Box 35, Folder 23)
      - Beltzig, Stefan, 1991-1992 (Box 35, Folder 24)
      - Ben-Yahuda, Yahuda, 1968-1973 (Box 35, Folder 25-26)
      - Berger, Carl Brandt, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 27)
      - Bergman, Lauren, 2004-2007 (Box 35, Folder 28)
      - Berthot, Jake, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 29)
      - Bianchi, Ben, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 30)
      - Bollinger, Bill, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 31)
      - Bower, Gary, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 32)
      - Bowles, Rowell, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 33)
      - Bramblett, Frank, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 34)
      - Brandt, Sharon, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 35)
      - Branson, Ortho D., 2006 (Box 35, Folder 36)
      - Brecht, Maja Suzanne, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 37)
      - Bronsteen, Earl, 2000 (Box 35, Folder 38)
      - Brooks, Bruce W., 1993-1995 (Box 35, Folder 39)
      - Brown, Ross A., 1992 (Box 35, Folder 40)
      - Brunetti, Erik, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 41)
      - Buechner, Thomas S., 1993-1996 (Box 35, Folder 42)
      - Buehner, Fritz, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 43)
      - Bultot, Roger, 1996-2006 (Box 35, Folder 44)
      - Butcher, Steve, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 45)
      - Capps, Kenneth, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 46)
      - Carlisle, Tamara, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 47)
      - Cash, Sidney, 2012 (Box 35, Folder 48)
      - Caulfield, Patrick, 1970s (Box 35, Folder 49)
      - Chang, Kuan, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 50)
      - Chansky, Matt, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 51)
      - Chao, Bruce, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 52)
      - Chapin, Steve, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 53)
      - Chiang, Paul, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 54)
      - Chitjian, Tigran, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 55)
      - Cibula, Ellen, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 56)
      - Clark, Ronald, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 57)
      - Clarke, John Clem, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 58)
      - Corrodi, Mark, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 59)
      - Creecy, Herbert, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 60)
      - Cuevas, Joseph, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 61)
      - Cuni, Pedro, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 62)
      - Davis, John, 2003 (Box 35, Folder 63)
      - Davies, Sally, 1995-2000 (Box 35, Folder 64)
      - Depasquale, James, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 65)
      - Deschamps, François, 1991-1993 (Box 35, Folder 66)
      - DiDonna, Porfirio, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 67)
      - Diller, Ben, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 68)
      - D'Orazio, Jon, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 69)
      - Durlach, David, 1990s (Box 35, Folder 70)
      - Dworkowitz, Alan, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 71)
      - Eckstein, Berry Morton, undated (Box 35, Folder 72)
      - Eisenstein, Avi, 1997 (Box 35, Folder 73)
      - Edwards, Benjamin, 1990s (Box 35, Folder 74)
      - Erró, 1976-2004 (Box 35, Folder 75)
      - Escher, Fred, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 76)
      - Evans, Bruce, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 77)
      - Evans, Laura, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 78)
      - Everett, Bruce, 1970s-2002 (Box 35, Folder 79)
      - Eversley, Frederick J., 1970 (Box 35, Folder 80)
      - Fagg, Rebecca, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 81)
      - Falsetta, Vincent, 1995 (Box 35, Folder 82)
      - Farber, Manny, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 83)
      - Finneran, William, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 84)
      - Fiorda, Daniel, 2000-2008 (Box 35, Folder 85)
      - Fischer, R. M., 1977 (Box 35, Folder 86)
      - Fish, Tom, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 87)
      - Flinn, Robert, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 88)
      - Ford, Francis, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 89)
      - Fox, Carson, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 90)
      - Frank, Richard, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 91)
      - Gabrielese, Peter, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Galles, Arie A., 1980 (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Geiger, Steven, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Gniewek, Robert, 1980s (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Goldstein, Jack, 1972-2003 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Goldstein, Phil, 2000-2003 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Grigorovich, Vladimir, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Gunther, Perry, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Hall, D. J., 1980s-2005 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Ham, YounJoo, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Hamada, Hiroyuki, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Han, H. N., 1972-2003 (Box 36, Folder 12-15)
      - Hansen, Glen, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Havard, James, 1971 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Hebert, Tom, 1995 (Box 36, Folder 18)
      - Hendrix, Susan, 1999-2009 (Box 36, Folder 19)
      - Herbert, George, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 20)
      - Herfield, Phyllis, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 21)
      - Herman, Alan, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 22)
      - Heyer, Mark Jay, 1996-2002 (Box 36, Folder 23)
      - Heyman, Abigail, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Hoelscher, Jason, 1990 (Box 36, Folder 25)
      - Hoffman, Martin, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 26)
      - Hofmekler, Ori, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 27)
      - Holcomb, Susan, 1988 (Box 36, Folder 28)
      - Horelick, Lauren Anne, 2002-2004 (Box 36, Folder 29)
      - Horn, Gerald, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 30)
      - Hoschler, Richard, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 31)
      - Hrycun, George, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 32)
      - Hyman, Sylvia, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 33)
      - Inoue, Kazuko, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 34)
      - Ikawawa, Naoki, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 35)
      - Jacobs, Jim, 1976-1978 (Box 36, Folder 36)
      - Jacobson, Gary, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 37)
      - James, Nathan J., 1998 (Box 36, Folder 38)
      - Jano-Zenou, Jack, 1995-1997 (Box 36, Folder 39-40)
      - Jeffrey, Carlin, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 41)
      - Jelinek, David, 1997-1999 (Box 36, Folder 42)
      - Jiminez, Luis, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 43-45)
      - Jin, Ik-Song, 1998-2001 (Box 36, Folder 46)
      - Johnston, Matthew, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 47)
      - Joseph, Richard, 1983-1990 (Box 36, Folder 48)
      - Joyce, David, 1996-1997 (Box 36, Folder 49)
      - Judelson, David, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 50)
      - Kalina, Richard, 1972 (Box 36, Folder 51)
      - Kazlov, Brian, 1974-1991 (Box 36, Folder 52)
      - Kearns, Jerry, 1970s (Box 36, Folder 53)
      - Keith, Kit, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 54)
      - Kelly, Jay, 1993-2002 (Box 36, Folder 55)
      - Kelly, Patrick, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 56)
      - Kerlin, Sherry, 1983-1985 (Box 36, Folder 57)
      - Kerr, Ed, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 58)
      - Kiki, John, 2000-2008 (Box 36, Folder 59)
      - Kilcullen, Robert, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 60)
      - King, Tony, 1987-1994; Includes 1 USB flashdrive (Box 36, Folder 61)
      - Kipniss, Robert, 1991-1994 (Box 36, Folder 62)
      - Knafo, Hai, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 63)
      - Kogge, Robert, 1990s (Box 36, Folder 64)
      - Kosianski, Leonard, 2007-2010 (Box 36, Folder 65)
      - Kreuger, Jack, circa 1970 (Box 36, Folder 66)
      - Kubina, Jerzy, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 67)
      - Kudo, Guty, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 68)
      - Kuhr, Alexis, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 69)
      - Kustura, Ivan, 1994-1995 (Box 36, Folder 70)
      - Larsen, Steen Valde, 2003 (Box 36, Folder 71)
      - Laury, Micha, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 72)
      - Ledy, Ann, 2004 (Box 36, Folder 73)
      - Lee, Unju, 1978-2005 (Box 36, Folder 74)
      - Leigh, Harry, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 75)
      - Lentsch, Edward, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 76)
      - Levinson, Mon, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 77)
      - Lew, Jeffrey, 1970 (Box 36, Folder 78)
      - Lew, Leslie, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 79)
      - Lewellyn, Don, 1972-1980s (Box 36, Folder 80)
      - Li-Lan, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 81)
      - Lim, Choong-Sup, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 82)
      - Linden, Steve, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 83)
      - Linder, Tracy, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 84)
      - Lindlof, Ed, 1996-2011 (Box 36, Folder 85)
      - Lipski, Donald, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 86)
      - Littell, Ross, 1993 (Box 36, Folder 87)
      - Lomas, Raffael, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Lowe, Robert, 1980s-1990s (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Lutzke, Richard, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Mabe, Joni, 1990s (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - MacAdam, Jon, 2007-2009 (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Macauley, Thomas, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Mahaffey, Noel, 1970s-1980s (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Mahima, Akiko, 2008-2011 (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Manley, Bryn, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Maresca, Joseph, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Marx, Amy, 2008-2009 (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Mastracco, Vincent, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Maxwell, Dwayne, 1987-1993 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Mayercak, Zdeno, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Mazziotti, Mary M., 2011 (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Menchiari, Roberto, 1994-2004 (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Mercer, Sunni, 1997-2005 (Box 37, Folder 17)
      - Mihanesteanu, Lucian, 1999-2002 (Box 37, Folder 18)
      - Mikus, Eleanore, 1997-2009 (Box 37, Folder 19)
      - Milgrim, Charlene, 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 20)
      - Miller, Elliot, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 21)
      - Miller, Marc, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 22)
      - Minotto, Paul, 1997 (Box 37, Folder 23)
      - Moore, G. E., 1971 (Box 37, Folder 24)
      - Morais, Edmund, 1972 (Box 37, Folder 25)
      - Moran, Pat, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 26)
      - Morley, Malcom, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 27)
      - Motyka, Jo, 2005-2006 (Box 37, Folder 28)
      - Munding, Michael, 1994-1997 (Box 37, Folder 29)
      - Murphy, J. Francis, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 30)
      - Nagano, Yoko, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 31)
      - Nakagawa, Naoto, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 32)
      - Navarra, Douglas, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 33)
      - Neumuth, Mary, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 34)
      - Nitka, Louis, 1990s (Box 37, Folder 35)
      - Noble, Daniel, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 36)
      - Noguchi, Tokuo, 2004 (Box 37, Folder 37)
      - Novak, Lorie, 1983 (Box 37, Folder 38)
      - Nowlin, Oliver, 1980s-1994 (Box 37, Folder 39)
      - O'Brien, Dennis, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 40)
      - Olson, Tim, 2000-2001 (Box 37, Folder 41)
      - Opocensky, Pavel, 1990 (Box 37, Folder 42)
      - Orselli, Janet, 2010 (Box 37, Folder 43)
      - Ossi, James M., 1981-1993 (Box 37, Folder 44)
      - Oz, Avital, 1981-2007 (Box 37, Folder 45)
      - Palaia, Franc, 1993-1995 (Box 37, Folder 46)
      - Paschoal, Len T., 1996-1997 (Box 37, Folder 47)
      - Patrick, Joseph Alexander, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 48)
      - Perelman, Luis, 1969-2003 (Box 37, Folder 49)
      - Pettibone, Richard, 1984 (Box 37, Folder 50)
      - Peugh, R. Benton, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 51)
      - Pfosti, B. Herbert, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 52)
      - Piacentino, Gianni, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 53)
      - Piedilato, Andy, 2001-2007 (Box 37, Folder 54)
      - Poindexter, Ethel, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 55)
      - Posen, Stephen, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 56)
      - Pratt, Vernon, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 57)
      - Rabinowitz, Royden, 1970s (Box 37, Folder 58)
      - Ravitz, Mark, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 59)
      - Ray, Linda, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 60)
      - Reed, Carl A., 1990s (Box 37, Folder 61)
      - Reiback, Earl, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 62)
      - Rennels, Sig, 1970s (Box 37, Folder 63)
      - Richardson, Judy, 1996-2000 (Box 37, Folder 64)
      - Richert, Clark, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 65)
      - Ries, Wanda, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 66)
      - Rodriguez, Victor, 1990s (Box 37, Folder 67)
      - Rogers, Pamala, 1996 (Box 37, Folder 68)
      - Rogers, William, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 69)
      - Roje, Arsen, 2002 (Box 37, Folder 70)
      - Rosenberg, Edo, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 71)
      - Rosenfield, Leonard, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 72)
      - Roth, Cora H., 1998 (Box 37, Folder 73)
      - Roth, Frank, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 74)
      - Roth, Richard, 1969-1972 (Box 37, Folder 75)
      - Rowan, Carol, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 76)
      - Rubin, Jeffrey, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 77)
      - Rubins, Nancy, 1982 (Box 37, Folder 78)
      - Rudich, Richard, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 79)
      - Ruiz, Denis William (Wintersong), 1970 (Box 37, Folder 80)
      - Russell, Jeff, 1980 (Box 37, Folder 81)
      - Salfas, Dianne, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 82)
      - Sandman, Jo, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 83)
      - Sato, Masami, undated (Box 37, Folder 84)
      - Savage, W. Lee, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 85)
      - Schneir, Leonard, 1994-2001 (Box 37, Folder 86)
      - Schwartz, Buky, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 87)
      - Schwartz, Eric, 1974-1976 (Box 37, Folder 88)
      - Scott, Arden, 1981 (Box 37, Folder 89)
      - Senza, Gabrielle, 1991-1993 (Box 37, Folder 90)
      - Shaffer, Mary, 1988 (Box 37, Folder 91)
      - Shanbhag, Lei Zhang, 1995-1996 (Box 37, Folder 92)
      - Shaw, Karen, 1975 (Box 37, Folder 93)
      - Shedletsky, Stuart, 1970s (Box 37, Folder 94)
      - Shimooka, Takafumi, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 95)
      - Siler, Todd, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 96)
      - Silver, Steve, 1991 (Box 37, Folder 97)
      - Sinclair, Maryellen, 1991-2002 (Box 37, Folder 98)
      - Smith, Lawson, 1998 (Box 37, Folder 99)
      - Smith, Richard, 1974-1975 (Box 37, Folder 100-101)
      - Soffer, Sasson, 1970 (Box 37, Folder 102)
      - Soghor, William, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 103)
      - Sonmor, Kevin, 1994-1997 (Box 37, Folder 104)
      - Souza, Al, 1985 (Box 37, Folder 105)
      - Stamm, Ted, 1973 (Box 37, Folder 106)
      - Steihauer, Andrew, 1978 (Box 37, Folder 107)
      - Stever, Jorge, 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 108)
      - Stewart, William, circa 1969 (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Stickloon, R. G., 2006 (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Stone, Cynthia, 1991 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Stratford, Herb, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Sunseri, Don, 1975 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Suska, Cestmir, 1997-2009 (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Taylor, Richard, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Thorne, Patrick, 1990s (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Tobin, Steve, 1998 (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Troy, Richard, 1997 (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Tzannes, George, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Ursachi, Leonard, 1989-1994 (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Valenta, Barbara, 1993-1994 (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Venet, Bernar, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Victoria, Ted, 1974-1996 (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Von Ringelheim, Paul, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Wald, Carol, 1976 (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Weber, Eleanore, 1997-1999 (Box 38, Folder 18)
      - Weber, Idelle, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 19)
      - Weinstein, Jeffrey S., 1973 (Box 38, Folder 20)
      - Weir, Margi, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 21)
      - Weller, Ted, 2002-2007; Includes 3 electronic discs (CD) (Box 38, Folder 22)
      - Wheeler, Mary, 1982 (Box 38, Folder 23)
      - Wholley, Jay N., 1982 (Box 38, Folder 24)
      - Wideman, Robert, 1980s (Box 38, Folder 25)
      - Willis, Thornton, 1977 (Box 38, Folder 26)
      - Wohl, Robin, 1995-2003 (Box 38, Folder 27)
      - Wojcik, Gary, 1975-1976 (Box 38, Folder 28)
      - Wolfe, Gerald, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 29)
      - Woodburn, Stephen B., 1976 (Box 38, Folder 30)
      - Wulke, Joy, 1988 (Box 38, Folder 31)
      - Wurtzel, Daniel, 1992 (Box 38, Folder 32)
      - Yalovitz-Blankenship, Maxine, 1998-2003 (Box 38, Folder 33)
      - Young, John T., 1991-1996 (Box 38, Folder 34)
      - Zaig, David, 1989 (Box 38, Folder 35)
      - Zenkius, Jerry, 1974 (Box 38, Folder 36)
      - Zhang, Naijun, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 37)
- Printed Material, 1963-2014; Series 5; 5.2 Linear feet Boxes 38-44, 80, OV 88-OV 90
  Printed material produced by OK Harris Works of Art includes a complete set of exhibition announcements. Scattered among the announcements are a small number of invitations to gallery events including receptions, openings, a sock hop, a few performances, concerts, and parties. Although OK Harris presented as many as six concurrent exhibitions every six weeks, the number of exhibition catalogs and posters is very small, reflecting the tight schedule. Earlier printed material is particularly creative and unique, each announcement carving out an attention getting and occasionally humorous approach, some with modest shock value. The graphics are usually interesting as are the materials used. Over time, OK Harris's printed items became more traditional with postcard style announcements predominating.
  Printed material produced by others consists of periodicals, books, exibition catalogs, guidebooks and clippings. Most are about or mention Ivan Karp, Marilyn Karp, gallery artists and exhibitions. Exhibition catalogs feature works by OK Harris artists and works loaned by the gallery; also included are catalogs of shows for which Karp was a juror. Miscellaneous items relate to events with Karp as a speaker or juror. Scattered throughout is general information about SoHo and Photo-realism. Exhibition Posters are: "Amerikanske Realister," Randers Kunstmuseum; "Ivan C. Karp Photographs," California State University, Long Beach; "Los Angeles Heute," Amerika Haus; and "Ivan Karp: The Face of Contemporary Art," Hong Kong Institute for Promotion of Chinese Culture. Miscellaneous posters are: "Walt Disney" by W. Fawcett, "Marihuana" ( sic), "Artist being Booked for Exhibiting Without Talent," "Biscuits" by Manuel Hughes, and "Davis Cone."
  Additional printed items generated by OK Harris Works of Art and other sources are found among administrative files (Series 2), artists' files (Series 3), and the Ivan C. Karp papers (Series 8).
  This series is arranged as 2 subseries:
  5.1: Produced by OK Harris Works of Art, 1969-2014
  5.2: Produced by Others, 1963-2012
  - Produced by OK Harris Works of Art, 1969-2014; 5.1
    - Exhibition Schedules, 1969-2014 (Box 38, Folder 38)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 1969 October-1981 July; Oversized material housed in Box 80 (Box 38, Folder 39-50)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 1981 September-1992 July (Box 39, Folder 1-11)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 1992 September-2003 September (Box 40, Folder 1-11)
    - Exhibition Announcements, 2003 September-2014 April (Box 41, Folder 1-11)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1974-2010 (Box 41, Folder 12-13)
    - Exhibition Posters, 1972-1990; undated (Box 41, Folder 14)
      Oversized material housed in OV 88
    - Oversized Exhibition Announcements from Box 38, Folder 39), 1970 (Box 80)
    - Oversized Exhibition Posters from Box 41, Folder 14, undated; 1972-1990 (Box OV 88)
  - Produced by Others, 1963-2013; 5.2
    - Articles, undated; 1963-2012 (Box 42, Folder 1-15)
    - Books, 1985-2010; undated (Box 42, Folder 16-20)
    - Exhibition Catalogs, 1963-2012 (Box 43, Folder 1-15)
    - Exhibition Posters, 1973-1996; Oversized material housed in OV 89 (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Guidebooks, 1978-2013 (Box 43, Folder 17-20)
    - Guidebooks, 2004-2013 (Box 44, Folder 1-3)
    - Invitations to September 11 Memorial Exhibitions, 2002 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous Printed Items, 1975-2008 (Box 44, Folder 5-7)
    - Periodicals, 1972-2009 (Box 44, Folder 8-10)
    - Posters, Miscellaneous, undated; 1996; Oversized material housed in OV 90 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Oversized Exhibition Posters from Box 43, Folder 16, 1973-1996 (Box OV 89)
    - Oversized Posters, Miscellaneous, from Box 44, Folder 11, undated; 1996 (Box OV 90)
- Artwork, 1970s-circa 1980s; Series 6; 0.8 Linear feet Box 44, OV 81-OV 87